Harrison Gerry

Junior front end developer SW London, Teddington (+44) 07526 890577 | h3gerry@googlemail.com GitHub | LinkedIn | Portfolio

Personal Profile

I have had a long standing interest in technology. As an avid gamer I have interacted with many who also share this passion and this is what drew me into learning how to code. I have always wanted to understand how the programs that are so deeply integrated into our lives and how they can be improved upon into the future.

I have recently finished a software development bootcamp that has taught me essential concepts of coding. I have enjoyed learning how to algorithmically solve problems and utilizing the tools provided by programming languages. I work well in teams and am a confident communicator.

I look forward to entering my first role in the field and gaining an understanding of the various specializations available to me. I am excited about its constantly evolving nature with many challenges to solve.

Employment History

04/2022-11/2023 Boethius Boffee Ltd, London - Barista

- Serving up to 120 customers a day and providing a comfortable and efficient service.
- Collaborating with colleagues with clear communication to ensure that orders were delivered in a timely and correct manner.
- Covered for colleagues who were unable to work to prevent staff shortage.

03/2021 - 12/2021 UCB, Slough - Analytical scientist

- Careful cataloging test results gained from sensitive and unique samples.
- Following procedure in order to get repeatable and consistent results.
- Working as a team on an under budgeted project to produce results under strict time constraints.
- Analyzing errors on equipment and referencing the documentation to find the correct way forwards.

07/2018 - 08/2020 National Physical Laboratory, Location - Junior research scientist

- Ordering stock to ensure that testing operations run smoothly.
- Being responsible for sensitive and expensive laboratory equipment and materials.

Working on a project from the perspective of a user who is unfamiliar with a product and providing feedback on its usability. The customer was pleased with the result.

Education

11/2023 - 02/2024 | Software development course, Just IT Training Ltd, London Digital Skills Bootcamp: Software Development A twelve week intensive bootcamp covering the fundamentals of Web and Software development.

07/2018 - 08/2020 | NPL (provided by CSR group), Teddington, Greater London BTEC Level 3 Diploma: Applied Science (Merit, Merit) Level 3 Laboratory Technician Standard

07/2012 - 06/2017 | Teddington School, Greater London GCSEs: 9 GCSEs including Maths (7), Physics (A), Biology (A)

IT Skills

Software Development Skills: GitHub - MS Teams

Web Technology: HTML - CSS

Core Programming Languages: Python - JavaScript - MySQL

Projects:

- A program using JavaScript that facilitates easy creation of JS objects
- An application using python and MySQL that tracks ingredients and allows easy access to potion making for use in tabletop role playing games

Interests

I built my own gaming PC to run highly modified games.

I spend time in communities that have a high proportion of developers, security specialists and people involved in devops.

I play in an in person roleplaying game weekly (Dungeons and Dragons) where a team and I work together to overcome challenges laid out before us by the Game master. These challenges range from puzzles to tactical combat to solving political disputes, which we must find innovative solutions for.

I test my friends' games to find softlocks, visual bugs and poor balance. I then record the scenario and steps leading up to the bug in order to provide them the best chance of squashing the bug.